無限的愛
O God, how endless is Your love
Oh Dios, ¡inconmensurable es Tu amor!
哦！主的愛何其無限！
O God, how endless is Your love!
Oh Dios, ¡inconmensurable es Tu amor!
主恩賜夜夜都如新
Your gifts are every evening new
Nuevos son Tus dones cada noche
主憐憫日日美又善
And morning mercies from above
Y cada mañana Tus misericordias de lo Alto
如黎明晶瑩的朝露
gently distill like early dew
Destilando tiernamente como rocío matutino
祢展開絲絨般夜幕
You spread the curtain of the night
Tú extiendes la tienda de la noche
護衛使我安然入夢
great Guardian of my sleeping hours
Como el Gran Guardián de mis horas de sueño
晨光夜色遵主而行
Your sovereign word restores the light
Tu soberana Palabra hace la luz
我靈亦隨甦醒
and quickens all my powers
Y me das nuevos bríos
我願謹遵主的吩咐
I yield my power to Your command
Mis potencias rindo a Tu voluntad
一生年日奉獻為主
to You I consecrate my days
Los días de mi vida consagro a Ti
因主賜不變的庇護
Eternal blessings from Your hand
¡Estas eternas bendiciones de Tu mano
配得永遠讚美歡呼──讚美主！
demand eternal songs of praise, songs of praise!
Demandan también alabanzas eternas, alabanzas eternas!
哦！主的愛何其無限！
O God, how endless is Your love!
Oh Dios, ¡inconmensurable es Tu amor!
主恩賜夜夜都如新
Your gifts are every evening new
Nuevos son Tus dones cada noche
主憐憫日日美又善
And morning mercies from above
Y cada mañana Tus misericordias de lo Alto
如黎明晶瑩的朝露
gently distill like early dew
Destilando tiernamente como rocío matutino
哦！主的愛何其無限！
O God, how endless is Your love!
Oh Dios, ¡inconmensurable es Tu amor!
主恩賜夜夜都如新
Your gifts are every evening new
Nuevos son Tus dones cada noche
主憐憫日日美又善
And morning mercies from above
Y cada mañana Tus misericordias de lo Alto
如黎明晶瑩的朝露
gently distill like early dew
Destilando tiernamente como rocío matutino
哦！主的愛何其無限！
O God, how endless is Your love!
Oh Dios, ¡inconmensurable es Tu amor!